<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Terminal</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Terminal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Goals for 2025</title>
      <link>/posts/goal-for-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/goal-for-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;as 2024 is comming to an end I want to be clear on my goals for 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe the best way to start a year is to have a crystalclear image or vission of what you want to achieve and maybe more importantly how you want to achieve it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ive been doing this since the end of 2019 getting into 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but for some reason, I always fall off by february or march&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;as 2024 is comming to an end I want to be clear on my goals for 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe the best way to start a year is to have a crystalclear image or vission of what you want to achieve and maybe more importantly how you want to achieve it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ive been doing this since the end of 2019 getting into 2020&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but for some reason, I always fall off by february or march&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;not this year&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;im DONE with breaking my own promises&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe a huge common mistake in setting &amp;ldquo;new year resolutions&amp;rdquo; is not being spesific enough, and not having a strong enough reason why&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if your why is strong enough and you can remind yourself of it everyday&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;youre more likely to win&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;secondly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;instead of wishing or hoping for x outcome&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;set a clear plan for the work youre going to do to get to that destination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to build a better physique this year&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;instead of just going to the gym randomly and eating healthier&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have a clear plan as to what I MUST do every day of 2025&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Im signing up a subscription with a fitness coach that tells me how to train and how to eat or what to eat&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and I just follow his rules EVERY DAMN DAY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this is easier said than done&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but my reason WHY is that ive been trying for too long now&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and I realize that trying is not going to get you there&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;its not enough doing your best, you have to do what &lt;em&gt;REQUIRED&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;SO goal number 1: EAT, SLEEP, AND TRAIN JUST LIKE MY COACH TELLS ME TO, LIKE MY LIFE DEPENDS ON IT NO MERCY&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and honestly I think thats enough&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if youre having to many goals, life is going to get cluttered and youre at higher risk of falling off&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I believe its better to set one big goal that 100 small ones&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also have a few internet mentors, that im listening to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;there are many people I look up to, but to keep it simple, three mentors for 2025:
!&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;/images/Pasted%20image%2020241208142105.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dr. Jordan B. Peterson, David Goggins and Alex Hormozi&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;find your mentors&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and lastly&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanna read more books, im a slow reader, but I find it more valuable to spend a good amount of time understanding one book before hopping to the next, even reading the same book multiple times&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;its been a hype recently speedreading 1 book a week,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;thats great! But how much have you learned?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;unless youre reading to change your behavior youre not actually learning&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so my books for 2025:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Outwitting The Devil by Napoleon Hill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mastery by Robert Greene&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How to win friends and influence people by Dale Carnegie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Power Of Now by  Eckhart Tolle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Way Of The Superior Man by David Deida&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;12 Rules for Life by Jordan Peterson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Gospel of John&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proverbs in the Bible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We who wrestle with God by Dr. Jordan B. Peterson&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cant Hurt Me by David Goggins&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;thats 9 books some ive read before, and some I havent&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but ive decided that this is going to be a life changing year&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;reading is just a habbit im going to get used to while commuting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-why&#34;&gt;the why&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;there are many other things I want to do&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but this year will be the year of self improvement for me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;getting back on the track of becoming the best version of my self&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was on a journey like this when I was 17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but ive fallen of the train and ive been left behind&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;now im 22 years old and nowhere close the person I imagined id be at 22 when I was 17&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;which is a frightening realisation, this means If I continue, Ill be 27 still not closer to the person I wish to become&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so I must take action&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the most important tasts for me is eating healthy, getting enough sleep, going to the gym and reading books and learning&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Latenight thoughts</title>
      <link>/posts/latenight-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/latenight-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used to have an insane drive and motivation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;no mercy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to be rich, strong, handsome, and everything that could make me a stronger opponent in the game of life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but sometimes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the desire fades away&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s been happening lately&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to grasp why&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but it&amp;rsquo;s pretty obvious&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you&amp;rsquo;re not hungry when you&amp;rsquo;re satisfied&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you don&amp;rsquo;t wanna go hunt down a bison if you&amp;rsquo;ve just eaten pizza&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I used to have an insane drive and motivation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;no mercy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I wanted to be rich, strong, handsome, and everything that could make me a stronger opponent in the game of life&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but sometimes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the desire fades away&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s been happening lately&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and it&amp;rsquo;s hard to grasp why&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but it&amp;rsquo;s pretty obvious&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you&amp;rsquo;re not hungry when you&amp;rsquo;re satisfied&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you don&amp;rsquo;t wanna go hunt down a bison if you&amp;rsquo;ve just eaten pizza&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that&amp;rsquo;s it&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;dopamine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the instant gratification tricking you into thinking that you&amp;rsquo;re fine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;tricking you into believing that what you have is enough&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;when in reality, you have a deep starving hole in you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but what happens once you starve yourself from that dopamine?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for me it&amp;rsquo;s clear&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the hunger, the desire sneaks back and becomes louder!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hunger and desire are what&amp;rsquo;s going to drive you to greatness&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s your reason why,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s do or die&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want success in life, you need to want it more than anything else&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;that feeling of never being satisfied, always hungry for more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instant gratification and dopamine put a silence on the desire for greatness&lt;br&gt;
because, for a moment, you feel like you have what you want already.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but deep down, you know you&amp;rsquo;re missing something&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;something is not right&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;there is an empty void inside of you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;an emptiness that screams louder in the night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and even louder when you don&amp;rsquo;t have instant dopamine easily available to shut it down&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the problem is not the alcohol, porn, junk food, candy, or the drugs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the problem is that you have a void that needs to be filled&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;and you&amp;rsquo;re going for the easy quick fix&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have made a great fall in the battle of life, and surgery is necessary to heal the wound, but instead, you keep overdosing on painkillers to numb it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The painkillers wear off, and you&amp;rsquo;re back where you started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;so you run back to the painkillers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;something ain&amp;rsquo;t right&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this is not working&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s easier to fill the void with something that&amp;rsquo;s instant and temporary&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;rather than something that&amp;rsquo;s going to take a long time but will last a lifetime&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;if you starve yourself from that instant gratification, you only have one option available&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the long-term fix&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you realize that you must go through the surgery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s going to hurt&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but it&amp;rsquo;s the only right answer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s the thing that&amp;rsquo;s actually going to make you the person you want to become&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;your true dreams and desires that have been forgotten and buried deep down under painkillers, quick fixes, and dopamine&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;once you starve yourself from the temptations&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the hunger will sneak back to you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;you may not know your true mission in life now&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but if you starve yourself long enough&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;take in the silence&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;be patient&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;soon enough&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;with enough eagerness&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it will come to you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;eventually, it will all make sense&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the hunger that&amp;rsquo;s going to make you ready to fight&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to fight any battle you have to go through in order to become what you truly want&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;your desire is back, you&amp;rsquo;re back to your true self again,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s going to be brutal,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s going to be painful&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;but if nobody has told you yet&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;life is to be lived&lt;br&gt;
and living is painful sometimes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ACTIONSTEP: CUT OUT THE INSTANT DOPAMINE FOR 60 DAYS, AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;pro tip 1. Change your behaviour, rather than removing them. You&amp;rsquo;ll feel empty when you take away your dopamine habits, its like addictions, change porn with reading, change junkfood with healthy food&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;pro tip 2. To change your behaviour, change your environment, cant sit down and focus on a book? Go to the library. Its hard to eat healthy? Eat at home rather than going out&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;pro tip 3. Be patient. Change takes time, and is often painfull. It takes longer and is more painful than we can imagine, thats why 99% off people that try to change their life quit along the way before anything changes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;expect-it-to-be-hard-expect-it-to-take-a-horribly-long-time-and-expect-that-youre-going-to-feel-the-urge-to-give-up-but-you-will-not-give-up-because-your-life-depends-on-it&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;EXPECT IT TO BE HARD. EXPECT IT TO TAKE A HORRIBLY LONG TIME. AND EXPECT THAT YOU&amp;rsquo;RE GOING TO FEEL THE URGE TO GIVE UP. BUT YOU WILL NOT GIVE UP BECAUSE YOUR LIFE DEPENDS ON IT!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;good-luck&#34;&gt;**GOOD LUCK!&lt;/h2&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to my Blog</title>
      <link>/posts/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-is-just-a-test&#34;&gt;this is just a test&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;memento mori&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;h1 id=&#34;this-is-just-a-test&#34;&gt;this is just a test&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;memento mori&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
